var questions = [
  {
    question: "1. What is the name of the triangle with no equal sides?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "Scalene",
        option2: "Caitlyn",
        option3: "Galen",
      },
    ],
    answer: "Scalene",
  },
  {
    question: "2. How many dimensions does have a triangle?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "4",
        option2: "3",
        option3: "2",
      },
    ],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "3. What is the sum of the anglesin the triangle?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "270 degrees",
        option2: "180 degrees",
        option3: "90 degrees",
      },
    ],
    answer: "180 degrees",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4. The side opposite to the right angle in right angled triangle is called? ",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "Base",
        option2: "Perpendicular",
        option3: "Hypotenuse",
      },
    ],
    answer: "Hypotenuse",
  },
  {
    question: "5. The perimeter of scalene triangle with the sides a,b,c is?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "a+b+c",
        option3: "2a",
        option3: "None of these",
      },
    ],
    answer: "a+b+c",
  },
  {
    question: "6. Which of the set of three sides can't form a triangle?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "5cm,6cm,7cm",
        option2: "5cm,8cm,15cm",
        option3: "8cm,15cm,18cm",
      },
    ],
    answer: "5cm,8cm,15cm",
  },
  {
    question: "7. A triangle with all angles are less than 90 degrees?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "Acute",
        option2: "Obtuse",
        option3: "Equilateral",
      },
    ],
    answer: "Acute",
  },
  {
    question: "8. Which center is equidistant from the vertices of a triangle?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "Incenter",
        option2: "Centroid",
        option3: "The circumcenter",
      },
    ],
    answer: "The circumcenter",
  },
  {
    question: "9. The correct formula to find the area of trinagle is?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "½ × base × height",
        option2: "½ × base + height",
        option3: "½ + base + height",
      },
    ],
    answer: "½ × base × height",
  },
  {
    question:
      "10. What's the name of the type of maths that studies the sides and angles of triangles?",
    options: [
      {
        option1: "Geometery",
        option2: "Trigonometry",
        option3: "Algebra",
      },
    ],
    answer: "Trigonometry",
  },
];
